Guide to the King County Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- King County Nurses Association records, 1959-1989; 3049-004; 9.12 cubic feet 8 boxes and 1 Vertical File
  - NURSE OF THE YEAR AWARD COMMITTEE, 1978-1985; SUBGROUP 11 (Box-folder 6/13-20)
    - 1984 Nurse of the Year (Box-folder 6/18)
    - 1985 Nurse of the Year (Box-folder 6/19)
    - American Nurses Association and Washington State Nurses Association Award Nominations, 1985 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - NURSE PRACTICE COMMITTEE, 1973-1987; SUBGROUP 12 (Box-folder 6/21-28)
    Contains records related to education on issues relevant to nursing practice, including records of the School Health Subcommittee whose activities included engagement with the Seattle School Nurses' Association and the Seattle School Board on issues related to the health of students in primary and secondary school.
    - Assorted Resources on Healthcare, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Membership Lists, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - "Nursing: A Role to be Communicated" Workshop, 1979 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Programming, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1979 June-1986 May (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Program Report, 1980 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - Questionnaires, approximately 1987 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - SCHOOL HEALTH SUBCOMMITTEE, 1976-1987; SUB-SUBGROUP A (Box-folder 6/29-32)
        - Correspondence and Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1976-1980 (Box-folder 6/29)
          Includes records from the Seattle School Nurses' Association
        - Correspondence and Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1976-1980 (Box-folder 6/30)
        - Resources on School Nurses and Student Health Services (1 of 2), 1979-1987 (Box-folder 6/31)
        - Resources on School Nurses and Student Health Services (2 of 2), 1979-1987 (Box-folder 6/32)
  - PROGRAM COMMITTEE, 1972-1986; SUBGROUP 13 (Box-folder 6/33-7/7)
    Contains planning and publicity records for the KCNA quarterly district meeting and annual All Day Event, coordinated by the All Day Event Task Force.
    - District Meetings Protocol, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Annual Meeting Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Annual Meeting Spring, 1979 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Door Prize Info, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Winter District Meeting, 1981 (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Spring Banquet Program Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 6/38)
    - Fall District Program Meeting, 1981 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Winter District Meeting, 1982 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Spring Banquet Program Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 6/41)
    - Fall District Program Meeting, 1982 (Box-folder 6/42)
    - Winter District Program Meeting, 1983 (Box-folder 6/43)
    - Spring Banquet Planning, 1983 (Box-folder 6/44)
    - Fall District Meeting Planning, 1983 (Box-folder 6/45)
    - Winter District Meeting Planning and Evaluations, 1984 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Spring Banquet Program Planning, 1984 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Winter District Meeting Program Planning, 1985 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Spring District Meeting and Awards Banquet Planning, 1985 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Winter District Meeting, 1986 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Spring Banquet, 1986 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Program Committee Meeting Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - ALL DAY EVENT TASK FORCE, 1984-1986; SUB-SUBGROUP A (Box-folder 7/8-16, 8/19-22)
        - All Day Event Lesson Plan Proposals, 1986 (Box-folder 8/19)
        - 1984 Fall All Day Event Planning (1 of 2) (Box-folder 7/8)
        - 1984 Fall All Day Event Planning (2 of 2) (Box-folder 7/9)
        - Fall Program Planning: Resource Files on Related Programming (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Fall Program Planning: Resource Files on Related Programming (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 7/11)
        - 1985 Conference Planning Materials: Print Program and Advertising (1 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 8/20)
        - 1985 Conference Planning Materials: Program Proposals (2 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 8/21)
        - 1985 Conference Planning Materials: Program, Evaluations, and Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 8/22)
        - 1986 November All Day Event: Print Program Advertisements and Drafting (Box-folder 7/12)
        - 1986 November All Day Event Planning: Day of Logistics (Box-folder 7/13)
        - 1986 November All Day Event Planning: Program Evaluations (Box-folder 7/14)
        - 1986 November All Day Event: Program Planning and Presenters (Box-folder 7/15)
        - 1986 November All Day Event: Publicity (Box-folder 7/16)
  - PUBLIC RELATIONS COMMITTEE, 1979-1986; SUBGROUP 14 (Box-folder 7/17-21)
    Records include committee meeting materials and correspondence as well as records of the Special Public Relations Task Force formed to increase visibility of the nursing profession, including correspondence, press releases, nomination forms, and meeting minutes from April Nursing Recognition Month and KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day awards.
    - Meeting Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Public Relations Program Meeting Agenda, 1980 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Public Relations Council Meeting Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - King County Nurses Association Public Relations Information, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - SPECIAL PUBLIC RELATIONS TASK FORCE, 1980-1984; SUB-SUBGROUP A (Box-folder 7/22-8/2)
        - Nursing Recognition Month Planning: Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Publicity (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 7/22)
          Includes photograph of Ginny Kenyon [?]
        - Nursing Recognition Month Planning: Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Publicity (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 7/23)
        - KIXI Nurse of the Day Award Certificate, approximately 1980-1984 (Box-folder 7/24)
        - Nursing Recognition Month and Nurse of the Day Awardees, 1981 (Box-folder 7/25)
        - Nursing Recognition Month Press Sent to Pay N' Save Chairman Bean, 1981 (Box-folder 7/26)
        - Nurse of the Day Nominees, 1981 (Box-folder 7/27)
        - April Nursing Recognition Month, 1982 (Box-folder 7/28)
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Nominations (1 of 2), 1982 (Box-folder 7/29)
          Includes copies of the April as Nursing Recognition Month city and county proclamations.
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Nominations (2 of 2), 1982 (Box-folder 7/30)
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Fallout: Correspondence and Publicity, 1983 (Box-folder 7/31)
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Nominees: Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, Forms, 1983 (Box-folder 7/32)
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Honorees: Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Press Releases, 1984 (Box-folder 8/1)
        - KIXI Radio Nurse of the Day Nominations and Press Materials, 1984 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - INTERORGANIZATIONAL INVOLVEMENT, 1975-1986; SUBGROUP 15 (Box-folder 8/3-15)
    Contains the records of three organizations of which KCNA members served as representatives: the KCNA/King County Medical Society Interprofessional Committee, Home Health Services of Puget Sound Advisory Committee, and National Health Services Corps Jail Health Advisory Committee. Records include correspondence, subject files, reports, meeting minutes, bylaws, and other related material.
    - KING COUNTY NURSES ASSOCIATION/KING COUNTY MEDICAL SOCIETY INTERPROFESSIONAL COMMITTEE, 1975-1986; SUB-SUBGROUP A (Box-folder 8/3-8/12)
      - Resources on Nurse and Physician Joint Practice, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Committee Structure, Membership, and Issues, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Hospital Survey Replies, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Report to Board, 1977 July (Box-folder 8/8)
      - "Guidelines for the Development of a Joint Patient Care Committee", 1981-1983 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Survey of Interprofessional Communication in Hospitals, 1983 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - King County Medical Society "The Bulletin" With Article on Nurse/Physician Collaboration (page 10), 1984 October (Box-folder 8/11)
    - HOME HEALTH SERVICES OF PUGET SOUND ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1979-1981; SUB-SUBGROUP B (Box-folder 8/13-14)
      - Capitol Hill Day Center, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Minutes, Correspondence, and Bylaws, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - NATIONAL HEALTH SERVICES CORPS JAIL HEALTH ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1979-1985; SUB-SUBGROUP C (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Correspondence and Minutes, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 8/15)
- King County Nurses Association records, approximately 1970-1990; 3049-005; 7.98 cubic feet 7 boxes
  Certificate of Charter (1909); minutes, newsletters, financial records, grant files, task force files, photograph albums.
  Donated by Laura Peters, 11/14/1994.
  - Continuing Education Approval And Recognition Program Approved Courses (Box-folder 1)
  - Financial Records
  - Diaper Task Force (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 4)
  - Photographs
  - Proclamations
  - Board Of Directors Minutes
  - KCNA Legislative Council Subgroup
  - Board Of Directors (Box-folder 5)
  - Advocates
  - Advocates Newsletter 1980s (Box-folder 6)
  - Committee Files
  - Grant Files 1989
  - Position Papers 1980s
  - Oversize Scrapbooks (Box-folder 7)
  - Poster
  - Framed Charter Certificate 1909